boomtron.com 2016-05-11

# Privacy Policy – Boomtron.com

This privacy policy governs Boomtron.com.

**Information Collection**

TBOomtron may collect information from its users at any point on the site.  We are the sole owner of the information collected on Boomtron.com whether accessed via a web browser, a mobile device, a non-browser application, or email.

**Comments and Posts**

Boomtron users can choose to write comments or posts on the site. To leave a comment, users must submit a valid email address. Boomtron uses this information to screen out users who leave comments that violate its terms and conditions of use. Boomtron does not share user information with any other organization.

**Cookies**

Boomtron  may use cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. Session ID cookies terminate as soon as the user closes the browser. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help instructions.

**Third-Party Cookies**

Boomtron uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when you visit Boomtron.com. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Third-party advertisers’ use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies. Boomtron has no access to or control over these cookies once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

**Log Files**

Like most websites, our servers use log files. These log file records include Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. Boomtron uses this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. Boomtron may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though Boomtron makes every effort to preserve user privacy, it may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein Boomtron has a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process.

**Links**

Boomtron publishes links to other sites. Please be aware that Boomtron is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. Boomtron encourages its users to be aware when they leave Boomtron and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Boomtron.

**Third-Party Advertising**

The advertisements appearing on Boomtron are delivered to users with a third-party ad server. Information about a user’s visit to Boomtron.com, such as number of times they have viewed an advertisement (but not username, date of birth, or any other personal information) is used to serve ads to users on this site.

**Information Collected Through Third-Party Sources**

This type of information is collected anonymously by approved third-party partners (such as online marketing firms, research companies, social media companies, ad targeting firms, and other partners). None of the information collected by these sources contains any personally identifying information. This type of information includes, but is not limited to:

Demographic information (gender, age, HHI, job title, interests, etc.)  
Advertising information (clicks, interactions, post-impression performance data)  
Social networking information (Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, etc.)  
Research information (data collected from partners)

**Children Under 13**

Boomtron is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or on Boomtron. Boomtron does not knowingly target advertising to or collection information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, do not use or provide information on Boomtron. If Boomtron learns it has collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, the information will be deleted.

**Visitors from outside the United States**

Boomtron’s  offices are located in the United States. If you visit the site from another country, please be aware that information you provide to us or that we obtain as a result of your use of the site may be processed in and transferred to the United States and will be subject to U.S. law. U.S. privacy and data protection laws may not be equivalent to the laws in your country of residence.

**Notification of Changes**

Whenever Boomtron changes its privacy policy, it will post those changes to this privacy statement.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact admin@boomtron.com
